XXXXXXX is a documentary film directed by Liliana Colombo.
A tarot card reading as a starting point.
A disruptive relationship as a point.
Translation of the cards' symbols to a joint.
Of the domestic exploration for finding my voice.
A fuzzy control system is a control system based on fuzzy logic – a mathematical system that analyzes analog input values in terms of  logical variables that take on
continuous values between 0 and 1, in contrast to classical or digital logic, which operates on discrete values of either 1 or 0 (true or false, respectively).
Fuzzy logic is widely used in machine control.
The term  "fuzzy" refers to the fact that the logic involved can deal with concepts that
cannot be expressed as the "true" or "false" but rather as "partially true".
Although alternative approaches such as genetic algorithms and neural networks can perform just as well as fuzzy logic in many cases, fuzzy logic has the advantage that the
solution to the problem can be cast in terms that human operators can understand, such that that their experience can be used in the design of the controller.
This makes it easier to mechanize tasks that are
already successfully performed by humans.